

AIDEN MORI

Full Stack Developer

https://aiden77mori.github.io/aiden-portfolio

Summary

I am a web and smart contract developer with a strong attention to detail and experience leading teams of front-end, back-end, and smart contract developers. My portfolio includes a variety of successful DeFi, NFT marketplace, and web3 projects, as well as games built on Ethereum, Polygon, and Binance Smart Chain. As a proficient developer, I have an extensive understanding of programming languages, frameworks, and database structures, and am skilled in analyzing and resolving intricate problems. I am dedicated to keeping up with the latest technology trends and committed to delivering quality work, making me an invaluable addition to any team.

Experience

Development Team Lead on The Blockchain Projects, KURONURI, Remote

Dec 2021 - Present

- As a blockchain development leader, I've created over 4 advanced products that integrate blockchain technology with real-world industries, providing users with significant value and benefits.
- Led a team of 5 developers in designing intuitive interfaces and implemented MLM system that resulted in a 30% increase in user retention and a 20% increase in referrals.
- Have developed intelligent algorithms and predictive models that seamlessly integrate with blockchain systems using AI technology; increased 30% efficiency and accuracy in delivering results.
- Accomplished in building one comprehensive ${\hbox{\it DeFi}}$ ecosystem, token generation and token ${\hbox{\it IDO}}$ platforms, as well as developing 2 NFT marketplaces including over 15 Web3 projects.
- Experienced in developing and integrating more than 5 Play-to-Earn games based on blockchain technology, and successfully created a Metaverse platform that has gained widespread user appeal.
- Full Stack Developer, INCARTA (Part-Time), Australia

July 2019 - Oct 2021

- · Through the utilization of innovative approaches to enhance patient monitoring and care, healthcare providers can access real-time data on patients' physiological parameters, which facilitates informed decision-making on the treatment options and leads to a remarkable 25% increase in patient care.
- · Achieved significant improvements in healthcare connectivity and integration by focusing on enhancing INCARTA's leading clinical records platform, Alarta (one of the most advanced cloud-based critical care medical record systems) and successfully integrating BioBeat with HL7 platform.
- · Had remained at the forefront of emerging trends in the field, including AI and machine learning, and have a proven track record of leveraging these technologies to drive continuous improvement in patient care.
- The project that I'd worked here has been especially useful during the COVID-19 pandemic, where virtual consultations and remote patient monitoring have become increasingly important.

- Contributed to the simplification of the home selling process, which can be a source of stress for many people, resulting in significant value-addition to users in their home selling journey as a developer on Australia's #1 real estate agent comparison site.
- Improved the website's **user interface** and **optimized its speed**, resulting in a 35% speed improvement and a **20**% increase in user engagement.
- Collaborated with the **data science team** to develop **algorithms** that matched over **80**% of our platform's users with top-performing agents, as a result, **25**% increase in customer satisfaction.
- I am proud to have contributed to this project and look forward to applying my knowledge and experience in my future career endeavors.

Software Engineer, Le Grand Co, Ltd (Internship), Japan

Apr 2016 - Apr 2017

Apr 2013 - Mar 2016

- Collaborated on an exciting content marketing and SEO project during my Legrand internship, resulting in a 40% increase in website traffic within the first month of implementation.
- Acquired valuable hands-on experience in digital marketing and software engineering at Legrand, working with a passionate and talented team committed to delivering high-quality services to clients.
- Overall, had a rewarding Legrand internship experience, working on various digital marketing and software engineering projects while developing skills and knowledge in the field.

Education

Osaka University

· Bachelor of Engineering

Skills

- Javascript
- Typescript
- React.js
- Angular

- Solidity
- Python
- Web3.js
- Node.js

- Express.js
- React Native
- Ionic
- Flutter